[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "The department must ensure that all students and faculty members have access to a broad ____ of learning resources.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With regret, we have had to cancel the upcoming program on \"The Nervous System\" ____ to an unavoidable change in schedules.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Everyone has the right to a standard of living ____ for the health and well-being of himself and of his family, including food, clothing, and shelter.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These notes are intended as a ____ introduction to some of the main ideas and methods of calculus.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you get a grade below C-, you will need to ____ the course for it to count at all on your major.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "By signing the pledge, students make a personal commitment to ____ energy and help contribute to Yale's goal of reducing greenhouse gases by 10 percent.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a ____ of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot dictate it.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is an excellent piece of work. You ____ your ideas very clearly.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is no ____ in the master plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the compulsory stage of education have insufficient ____ educational opportunities.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't prepare herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Caesar showed no reluctance to ____ the office of \"dictator for life\" in February 44 B.C.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first section of this ____ is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This situation is certain to improve over the next few years, given the ____ of research now being done on the effectiveness of complementary medicine.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ that led to the train crash are being investigated by the police.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Scientists ____ that most children born today in First World countries will see their 75th birthday.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many young people fill in the ____ between school and university by travelling around the world for a few months.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can't always ____ what happens to you, but you can always ____ how you react to what happens to you.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This project involves students in the ____ of learning in an attempt to enhance their skills and their successes across all areas of the course.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government official wrote to ____ that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I am often surprised by the ____ of some high school students. One of them yesterday did not know the name of the president of the USA.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Strict laws in Germany ____ the opening of shops on a Sunday.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Aqaba ____ (see fig. 11.6) would pump sea water during off-peak periods.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She ignored an ____ warning that she would be expelled if she did not start working harder.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Use ____ words and phrases; don't drain the energy of the interview by focusing on the negative.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "German businesses have started to ____ an increasing number of older people. They are often better, more reliable workers.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Forests are both an important part of the ____ ecosystem and an important resource of raw materials for lumber, paper, and fuelwood.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The naval and air forces failed to ____ their schedules and the carrier planes arrived a half hour later than expected.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The first and only ____ line of defense against the acquisition or use of \"suitcase nuclear weapons\" by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We must ____ and strengthen existing laws and institute new procedures aimed at terrorists and criminals.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Each student's ____ was so varied that I was unable to isolate common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has ____ published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The latter has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The minister was unwilling to ____ on the changes in the price of oil in the next few months.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is not a defect in the ____ of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base ____ the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It must be obvious what the primary theme of each section is, and how that theme connects with the paper's ____ theme.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Newspaper headline: MIT scientists ____ a new way to deliver gene therapy.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will facilitate growth and development in our ____ communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ method of learning vocabulary is to write words and their translations in a small notebook.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will need to form project teams of two or three students, and then it will be your responsibility to ____ meetings.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Smith starts out with a ____ idea of what she wants to achieve.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His ____ is that if we don't cut taxes, then unemployment will rise.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax ____ to analyze its finance methods.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The best survival ____ for one part of the organization is usually not the best ____ for another.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first item on the agenda is the proposal to ____ working hours to 42 per work.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A ____ defect in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Another reason to ____ student e-mail and internet usage is to ensure their safety.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The temperatures did not ____ as much this month as they did last month.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The future energy system will need to ____ the unacceptable risk that the present system places on the environment.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Any student who continues to do poor work or show a bad ____ is put on a contract. If the contract is broken, then the student is asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The explanation for this ____ decision lies in the immediate circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mrs Cho spoke on ____ of the Korean Parents Group and thanked the school for buying Korean books for the library.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This document will ____ some of the problems that could exist because the computer is unable to install updates for Windows Vista.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school will always ____ its policy of expelling students for repeated plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This policy includes how the instructor arrives at the semester grade for each student, including the ____ of grades given for papers, tests, hourly exams.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will need to request a ____ leave of absence with USC if you intend to be away from more than 3 days.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These tips do not relieve you of the ____ to read and follow the Instruction Booklet which is ONLY available on line this year!", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Nadeem has worked with FSU London since early 2004 as a permanent ____ of staff managing the Information Technology Systems.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many of the faculty and students we talked with wanted to remain ____ and asked that they not be listed by name in our report.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She is going to fail the ____ unless there is a drastic improvement in her efforts.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When they did investigations after 9-11, one of the major things that they came up with was that the various government agencies did not ____ the dots.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many of the students were unable to ____ the relevance of the mathematics they had learned and so could not make use of it.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Use this form when you need to ____ accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will ____ many difficulties but if you persist in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an image war, trying to ____ the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to ____ money fairly to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was little ____ that the government's plans to increase taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Research strongly supports the ____ that publishing houses lack sufficient diversity in both high and middle-level staff members.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material environment of Louisiana, it did not ____ the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Example: She doesn't have a very good ____ with her parents.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Over the course of her ____ in the program she has come a great distance from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students will need to ____ a spokesperson to speak for their group and come to an agreement about their decision.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the ____ between teachers, parents and students, and improve the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV broadcast the government will declare its ____ to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "World leaders met in Bali to discuss global warming. Many people say that the whole ____ was a waste of time and money.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government will ____ its announcement until it has up-to-date information.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Venus will next ____ in the night sky in August 2007.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Customers found no benefit in ____ -shopping, since price uniformity was nearly absolute.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Furthermore, the text of the paragraph should correspond to the ____ sentence.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The naval and air forces failed to ____ their schedules and the carrier planes arrived a half hour later than expected.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to ____ this issue.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The two companies have settled their ____ over patent issues and dropped legal actions.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Autumn is a time of ____ for home gardeners.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has two problems; ____ his inability to concentrate in class and his unwillingness to do homework.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Bogart and Methot got married and the result was total ____ for both of them.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The women did not ____ emotionally to the comedy, but the men did, Filipowicz concludes.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "At the same time, we believe that the ____ over prejudice and hatred is achieved one person at a time.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ minister has said that he has no plan to resign over the crisis in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her efforts have continued to ____ in the last few months. I think she may be having problems at home.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Do you ever feel like some Asian traditions suppress the need for communication or being able to freely ____ your emotions?", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to ____ poor work that is due to laziness and poor work that is due to inability.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "home"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is research that could eventually help in the ____ of certain kinds of cancer.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Despite all the money spend on cancer research there is little ____ of a cure being found in the near future.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Truman managed to win a narrow ____ with 49.5 percent of the popular vote.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The World Bank said China has the capacity to absorb the ____ of the recent international financial market fluctuations.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After the attacks of September 11, 2001, Pat Cornell turned her ____ to detecting and preventing terrorism.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At this point, I often wonder whether or not education is fulfilling its purpose. A great ____ of the so-called educated people do not think logically.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Farmers rotate their crops. This ____ that they do not grow the same thing on the same field for more than one year.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most common ____ of a cold is a runny nose.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Specifically, you ____ that you were not provided with academic adjustments and auxiliary aids, and were not provided access to other services and programs at the College.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the ____ did not acknowledge the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You must turn in the ____ by next Friday. There can be no delay.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and function of cities and ways planners solve ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A ____ problem for most western societies is how to integrate immigrants with different cultures and religious beliefs.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The points that you ____ should be proportional to the individual's contribution to your team for the quarter to date.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In most of Africa, for example, weaker institutions have failed to ____ restrictions on rulers and undemocratic power politics has been employed.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She is so passive in German class. It's no wonder that she can ____ speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If I make a ____ of England and Germany, I have to say I prefer Germany. The weather is better and the people are more friendly.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many talented local young people have had to forego graduate or professional education because of ____ of access to such programs.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has announced its ____ for the introduction of the new tax system over the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How did you decide that some items were ____ necessary?", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is ____ that you hand in the essay on time. If you don't, you will fail the course.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teachers allege that the school ____ is secretly planning to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Now ____ that a box contains one fair coin and one coin with a head on each side.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We know it's not 100% correct, but it's the best ____ that we can produce at this time.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Research into heart disease has revealed a clear pattern: those who smoke too much, drink too much and do not exercise enough are the most likely to ____ from it.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is ____ a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own domestic problems.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The third ____ of the writing process is when you revise your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction ____ junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is the single most important ____ a district judge can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "To include an image on your website, you will need to ____ the image into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ from Frankfurt to Oberursel is about 12 kilometers.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The pictures presented aspects of the objects they could not ____ from the equations alone.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is our ____ that the students were not given a fair hearing, and furthermore that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Less than 10% of students who need ____ skills education and don't get it survive in college.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Abortion is not a ____ right; it can be limited if the state wishes.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If men and women do ____ jobs they should earn ____ pay.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has lost the ____ to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, indeed devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Harvard is probably the most famous education ____ in the USA.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ authority in the country is the President.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is ____ impossible to get into university unless you have done well in school.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government took the ____ decision to decrease tax.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To ____ the highest positions in American politics it is necessary to come from a rich family.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing ____ when repeating the same strategy could be a road to utter disaster.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ way of attacking the security of computer programs is to feed them unexpected and deceptive inputs.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was not the ____ noise of the battle-front that night; every soldier knew that a something different was going to happen.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "One study found that anemia was a strong predictor of other serious problems that were not ____ at the time anemia was first detected.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She was able to ____ the Smartboard screen controls so that the presentation was visible to everyone.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the words 'uninterested ' and 'disinterested'.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Patience was not ____ in him, but he developed it under misfortune and opposition.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and ____ of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The result will be an ____ and substantial increase in the number of faculty of color who are tenured at this institution.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This fact demonstrates that immigrants are not ____ to learning the language of their new country.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The situation in Iraq continues to ____ the government's attention.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students and non-students alike can be criminally charged if they don't ____ with police orders to disperse from riot or crowd situations.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is too early to ____ whether the government's plan to reduce child poverty have been successful or not.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The need for regulation is quite evident today but was not ____ before the early years of the 20th century.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some types of ____ are dirty, dangerous or not well-paid. It is often poor immigrants to a country who take such jobs.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Bush administration has failed to ____ the matter urgently, spending only \ufffd\ufffd1.3 billion per year.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new government has promised not to ____ the mistakes of the previous one.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the new science building is not finished yet, but from the outside it looks great!", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Great Britain, Canada, and the United States do not intend to ____ the secret until means have been found to control the bomb.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree with the ____ that the earth is getting warmer because of human pollution.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lack of financial ____ is a significant constraint on the chances of success in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They simply decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that ____ (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some teachers believe that it is better to teach language to a class with students of ____ ability.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is the room where we store the science ____ ready for use in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I can ____ on a moderate income. I don't need lots of money.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The student was hardly active with the ____ and did not attempt to contribute.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Every ____ precaution has been taken to provide up-to-date, accurate information in this website.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Through much of the War, the U.S. and its Allies could not ____ a fully effective blockade against Germany.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "That doesn't mean I have a personality disorder because I conduct myself in a different ____ to different people.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government plans to introduce an ____ for long-term unemployed people to start looking for work again.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your group will need to investigate the ____ characteristics of your city (such as mountains and lakes).", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The best ____ of your essay is the fact that it was very easy to follow your line of argument.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He has ____ improved his writing but his problems with spelling persist.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will ____ the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will ____ the economic burden on society.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Distance learning is the most significant ____ occurring in higher education today.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most countries have a ____ by which parents can decide if a film is suitable for their children.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some students see no ____ for learning German - especially if they know they will only be in the country for a short time.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has lost the desire to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, ____ devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We were not able to ____ statistically significant differences in performance or quality.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may ____ in an erroneous diagnosis or an inappropriate control recommendation.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The weather ____ for tomorrow says that we can expect showers and a little weak sunshine.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Upon completion of your program requirements, you will need to apply for a ____ to teach in the state of Ohio.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It isn't the government's fault if people ____ advice to live healthily.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Remember that you will ____ your ecology poster to the rest of the class in tomorrow's lesson.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school received an anonymous email with complaints ____ one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For some older people the ____ to new technologies has not been very smooth.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Internet businesses will only be successful if they use the ____ of clear, easy, cheap, safe shopping.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is NOT a ____ statistic and you should simply ignore it.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "His observations were not ____ enough to conclude anything significant about nocturnal behaviour.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Because multicultural audiences will likely become more and more common, you will need to ____ cultural differences when you analyze your audience.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most scientists are more interested in the ____ of winning the Nobel Prize than the money they get for doing so.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The beauty of the telephone, and something that the telegraph lacked, was that it required no ____ to operate.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company was fined a large sum of money for attempting to ____ pollution regulations.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Follow these recommended times for storage in the freezer to enjoy the best quality in flavor and texture and to ____ good nutritive value.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In fact, most nations do not admit immigrants for ____ settlement.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to exert its ____ to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The results indicated that there was a ____ improvement in fluency, a slight improvement in accuracy, but no improvement in complexity.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She has a ____ in one eye that makes it difficult for her to read from the board.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "China is, indeed, going through a ____, but it is not a ____ from capitalism to communism.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance ____ is independent of maternal ____, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest ____ between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some institutions did not ____ these issues because they predicted them and dealt with them in advance.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is largely responsible for the ____ of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company made a ____ reduction in its workforce in order to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the key words used and the ____ claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It offers an ____ solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills minor as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As ancient pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to ____ methods to produce a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ was too much for some, and owners were forced to sell their homes at a reduced price.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a regular basis to ____ new understanding.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Since Ramadan emphasizes ____ aspects and since everyone eats dinner at the same time, Muslims often invite one another to share in the Ramadan evening.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "control"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "China did not ____ nuclear weapons. Having produced several hundred warheads, China stopped building up its military potential.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If submitted in other languages, an English version must ____ the submission.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its reluctance to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To learn a new word, it often helps to make an ____ of it in your mind.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He is the inevitable ____ for the leading role in the play. He's by far the best actor in the school.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government can ____ its message about the dangers of drinking if it increases the price of alcohol.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Google uses a ____ computer program to generate its lists of hits within a very short period of time.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was ____ the most significant function of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In our society, which is far from ____ in its beliefs and values, reaching consensus on any issue is significantly difficult.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her parents failed to ____ the bad influence of her new friends until it was too late.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right ____ of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It should be ____ that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the prime cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As ancient pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to develop methods to ____ a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This course list should ____ the number of credits and the grade option (grade, pass/fail, audit) for each enrolled student.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The test will be a ____ of reading comprehension passages and short writing texts.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will need to ____ project teams of two or three students, and then it will be your responsibility to organize meetings.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This certificate program is a series of fully online courses that will show you how to ____ and deliver a quality course via the Internet.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One ____ of the problem that no-one has yet considered is: Who is going to pay?", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ cannot guarantee the accuracy of the information or the appropriateness of any material that a student finds.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government's election ____ is a classic case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Workers will ____ to where wages are higher.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is a fact that ____ drivers have fewer accidents than reckless ones.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "However, you may also include a citation at a natural breaking point within the sentence, for ____ before a comma or a conjunction.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Poor diet itself is not a cause of scoliosis, but maintaining a healthy diet can ____ the symptoms of scoliosis.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is the single most important deed a district judge can perform in the ____ of his duties.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Blair will need to persuade the Americans that Europeans will no longer ____ Saddam to play games with the inspectors.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to enable him to make a ____ decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was a ridiculous fear, but she was unable to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This document explains how to ____ password protection from your Web site.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A close study of this ____ will reward any reader.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some students ____ that they can simultaneously watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are making ____ progress in learning English.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power ____ failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The President accepts full ____ for the decision to attempt the rescue.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The controversy resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to ____ the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The students decided to ____ in their attempt to fight bullying in the school.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Such web content does not necessarily ____ the opinions of the University administration.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Smartboard is an excellent ____ for teaching language.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The following information has been prepared to serve as a ____ to assist you in establishing criteria for a successful teaching practice.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "How can educators ____ instruction to maximize the learning of all students?", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The idea that there is ____ in nature is part of most world views.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ fits well with the fact that his mental health did not deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This will be a reading lesson. Please do not ____ it by trying to talk.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to use a more ____ approach to persuading people to eat less and keep fit.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase ____ tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not pleasant to ____ the results of a German victory in World War II.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We also want to speak openly about the question of whether the German radio should ____ so-called jazz music.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To justify their high salary, top managers like to ____ to the increased risk that they will lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She chose to ____ the hypothesis that there is an increased risk of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first exhaust all possibilities for Federal and ____ financial aid programs before seeking alternative loans.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to procure a variety of ____ to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no liberty without law, and no ____ law or legal system when liberty is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The online instructor must incorporate the best practices of traditional teaching without the ____ of face-to-face interaction.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Men and women of all ages ____ from a moderate amount of daily physical activity (for example: 30 minutes of brisk walking or 15 minutes of jogging).", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police chief set up a ____ whose task was to investigate the reasons for the shooting of the wrong man.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The two companies have settled their dispute over patent issues and dropped ____ actions.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's not winning or losing that is important in school sport, but the ____ in which you do it.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This section is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an ____ explore topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Congress is resolved to ____ online gambling in America.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I have no ____ of being a teacher when I leave school. I want to earn more money!", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is also notable that in Justice Brennan agreement he commented that the Board could not ____ books based on mere disapproval of their content.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The university has no obligation to refund the ____ after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The goals are to answer some of the most ____ questions to advance significantly our scientific knowledge about Mars.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of such abuse was increased poverty in Russia and lost belief in the fairness of governmental institutions.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While I don't present this as absolutely the ultimate ____ that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Terrorists ____ large areas of the country outside of the main towns.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors ____ that people eat 5 fruits or vegetables every day.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to speculate on future developments, we need to consider the actual and ____ effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Neither of the two strategies was ____ in terms of performance.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He had no good reason for being late, so he decided to ____ one.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is still ____ of a risk to purchase things on the internet.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ are largely satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To ____ the project, a special event will commence at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Being at least 18 years old is a necessary ____ for being registered to vote.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You should try new ____ for learning vocabulary. Your present one does not seem very successful.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a ____ search strategy has paid off.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not the government's ____ to tell its citizens how to live.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is bringing in a new law to require food manufacturers to label their products as high-, low- or ____ fat.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to trust your ____ as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Do not ____ all your energy in the first 20 minutes. Remember that the game lasts for half an hour!", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is the room where we store the science ____ ready for use in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I gave you ____ instructions not to open the box. Why did you disobey me?", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's a bit surprising at first, how easy it is to ____ such a huge object as the earth.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to focus not only on the skills and knowledge ____ to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more authentic tasks.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is during adolescence that clear gender differences arise which might ____ to the varying rates of depression.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most of Africa suffers to some ____ from similar issues: weak institutions, stagnant economies, ethnic conflict, etc.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Unfortunately, many drug users emerge from prison only to find themselves back there a few months later. This is because they cannot find or keep a job, and need to steal to ____ their drug-taking habits.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The private ____ offers many opportunities for students with a history or liberal arts background.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Trying to water-ski for the first time is difficult but if you keep practising, you will ____ learn how to do it.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Seminar is an intensive examination of ____ policy making in Washington.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors have not been able to establish the ____ cause of the patient's illness.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first ____ those principles and then consider the subsequent problems.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to defend his ____ against the competitive approach favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The decision on whether to shut down its nuclear power stations is ____ the most serious issues facing the government.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is essential that governments take ____ before making the decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Once you've chosen the course or courses you wish to take, you should contact COM so that we can ____ a place for you.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people do not see the ____ of trying to save money when interest rates are so low.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The older population of the U.S. and the world is growing rapidly, and these large numbers will represent a ____ challenge for society in general.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Furthermore, as an educational institution, the College cannot ignore the background and perspectives of its students and must attempt to promote teaching practices and a campus ____ that benefits and ensures the success of all of its learners.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "GeoRef is the most complete single ____ of literature references concerning active volcanoes.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people think that the USA invaded Iraq because of oil. The ____ is much more complicated than that.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Cole Conservatory evolves from a Music Department with a long ____ of exceptional training for students from all backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "However, no one ____ will be the sole reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The strategy used for the actual campaign was ____ different.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is noted that the university regulations stipulate that a course can be offered only if a ____ number of students is enrolled.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When dealing with a real, physical system such as a robot, however, this ____ is simply not practical.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government must not hesitate in taking harsh actions ____ communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not strain our friendship in the least, I wished to avoid ____ conflict.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot ____ with this law due to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Stopping work to look after a new-born child must not be allowed to interfere with a woman's ____ chances.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The contributors ____ that teaching is a gendered occupation with low status and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ was too much for some, and owners were forced to sell their homes at a reduced price.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most older cultures seem to accept volcanoes as a natural part of life and ____ their habits accordingly.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Lucy has been formed by the West Indies; she still is deeply influenced, yet she would resist and ____ that heritage.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ why he made such a foolish decision.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has made smooth ____ all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are ____ of much better grades if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you discover that you have the wrong textbook, you must ____ the source from which you purchased the book and make arrangements to exchange the book.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Typical conversations involve a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans ____ as they grow.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Several campus departments have been working to ____ the number of false alarms that result from controllable and mechanical factors.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The communication ____ is a computer, phone line, and modem; the student must have access to the necessary equipment.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But the mice did not undergo ____ cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "John has many strong opinions. You have to be sure not to let him ____ groupwork in class.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Matilda Thurston considered who was the most logical architect to ____ a proper campus for 200 students.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not extract ourselves and ____ our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These budgets must be very carefully designed as it is ____ difficult, if not impossible, to alter the amount of the award once it has been granted.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you plan for your child to attend the school, you must ____ an online request.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you cannot obtain such a statement, you must ____ that you have contacted your employer and that the employer was unable to assist you with the refund.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I think that everyone going for the maximum marks, the highest grades and the greatest possible output is not the best ____ for a well-rounded individual.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Applying the engineering feedback concept, we can search and reach the optimum ____ with a very small number of tests.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Did anyone manage to ____ question 11?", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When the earth is closest to the sun, the ____ between the earth and sun is 147000000k.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ a new campaign to reduce teenage drinking.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The naval and air forces failed to ____ their schedules and the carrier planes arrived a half hour later than expected.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "real"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government looks ____ to succeed in its objective to reduce child poverty by the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These grades denote that the student has attained an acceptable ____ of competence.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ between mother and child is said to be the strongest of any personal relationships.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "People have been trying for decades or maybe even centuries in an attempt to bring this ____ problem to an end.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This was a ____ attempt at addressing the issue, and not a very scholarly or intellectual attempt.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you ____ your efforts you have a good chance of exiting ESL at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The existence of such alternative measures was not imaginary; the Commission had already suggested ____ possibilities.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may result in an erroneous ____ or an inappropriate control recommendation.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This was not characteristic of Serbia alone; the population felt ____ frustration in other parts of Yugoslavia and in Eastern Europe.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Thanks to the accurate ____ of the witnesses, the police were able to identify the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Less than 10% of students who need ____ skills education and don't get it survive in college.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to ____ in the dispute over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I do not wish to ____ that she is lazy, but her work is often late and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All this progress was a ____ of the advance of technology and also of advances in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dmitrieva and Kuptsova adopt an ____ approach and understand culture as a realm of signs and meanings.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His ____ is that if we don't cut taxes, then unemployment will rise.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's a ____ problem, and its solutions will require new technology, policy, awareness and education.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Victims of terrorist attacks are usually given ____ by the government.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mr. Bush cannot answer Sheehan's question and he cannot justify the war of aggression ____ Iraq.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As long as the person did not ____ large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the effect on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Her grades are low because of her ____ inability to turn work in on time.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Could you use informal writing tasks to ____ thinking and learning?", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The data is ____ as some analysts measure this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is unpopular and is expected to ____ badly in the forthcoming election.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Specifically, you ____ that you were not provided with academic adjustments and auxiliary aids, and were not provided access to other services and programs at the College.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was also faced with difficult questions about the university's handling of the emergency and whether it did enough to ____ students.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A three-year Indian bachelor's degree is NOT ____ to a U.S. bachelor's degree.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two legal professionals who must ____ with the death penalty regularly.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was ____ that the business would fail. It was badly run, and the products it sold were overpriced and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy demand to ____ costs.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university follows a ____ policy of expelling any student caught plagiarizing.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government must continue to make every effort to ____ young people from becoming addicted to drugs.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum ____ for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is now obvious to almost everyone that the decision to invade Iraq was a very serious ____ of judgment.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The students decided to ____ in their attempt to fight bullying in the school.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the ____ for the upcoming talks on practical matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "domain", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The machine did not work properly because the person installing it did not ____ the instructions.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is not an ____ test for ESL beginners. It is far too difficult.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We must trust the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The boss took the ____ decision to close the factory for a week.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The principle behind this policy is that the rights of the individuals should be respected; subjects must ____ to participation in research.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her parents failed to ____ the bad influence of her new friends until it was too late.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There are ____ 100 days until your final examination. It's time you started working.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Can we ____ the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to protect the environment?", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is essential that governments take ____ before making the decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will ____ the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will ____ the economic burden on society.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Slavery is not an ____ which developed itself.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For the first time in history, the federal government will ____ college and university admissions.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My parents have decided to ____ me from eating in my room.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The donors specified that they would like to help hardworking students with ____ grades who deserve help.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "People who move from the countryside to a large city often take time to ____ to urban living.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can prevent a massive ____ of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Any student who is at least 13 years old on September 30 is ____ to enter the mathematics competition.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government should do more to ____ immigrants who do not speak English.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to ____ from the College.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The book focuses on the key ____ the family plays as teenagers navigate the difficult transition from childhood to adulthood.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must ____ against the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The number of students in the school will continue to ____ in the next few years as Frankfurt increases in popularity.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school is working on a ____ to give all students a portable computer for use in lessons.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The university plans to ____ a fund so that poorer students can attend.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students needed to ____ considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I've decided to ____ the idea of starting writing a book. I just don't have the time.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is set to reject the parents' request to ____ their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "UK airports have increased the quantity of security ____ since the terrorist attacks in London.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to avoid talking unless absolutely ____ for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This ____ is not rare: 99 percent of patients experience a phantom pain after an amputation.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is somewhat unusual considering the 1997 survey's ____ of 41%.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Google uses a ____ computer program to generate its lists of hits within a very short period of time.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is one of several errors that ____ that your account is not set up properly; this can be corrected only by University personnel.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Education has reduced the ____ at which the disease has spread throughout the population.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A simple and often effective ____ to reduce blood pressure is to reduce the volume of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant ____ of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and enormous ____ developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Education has reduced the rate at which the disease has ____ throughout the population.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The VFWF reserves the right to ____ additional funds if the amount of the grant is insufficient to fully meet the needs.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate poor work that is ____ to laziness and poor work that is ____ to inability.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You do not need to consider the whole of human psychology, but you should make a ____ between good excuses and bad excuses.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a symptom of a greater cultural ____ that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teacher made the ____ decision to take her class out to the playground and finish the lesson there.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is suitable for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The university plans to establish a ____ so that poorer students can attend.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is not a ____ in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The professor meets with each student for a half-hour private tutorial ____ three times during the semester.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You must enter the US using the visa document issued by the ____ you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "After about a year his family realized that this was not just a ____ and that he was serious about me and that we really cared about each other.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not all the decisions of the ____ have been welcomed by the workers.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police need to ____ more evidence before they can make any arrests.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As one of its many uses to ____ learning, the Internet is increasingly being used as a forum for students to give feedback to each other.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of the conflict remains very much in doubt.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not ____ ourselves and therefore our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive ____ exam.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady rise in the ____ of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and external factors influencing the career development of first ____ Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is known that organizations do not ____ readily or easily; many organizations that change do so in ways that are neither successful nor effective.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors advise people to ____ the number of eggs they eat to 2-3 per week.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most important criterion for selecting a research ____ is that you are really interested in it!", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The library is going to ____ a new electronic system for checking out books.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Those are the rules of the school and I expect you to ____ accordingly.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to the new law, smokers will now have to ____ the pleasure of a cigarette with their drink in a restaurant or bar.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The student must also have a ____ address within the 22 South Texas county area.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These facilities and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable ____ to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will need to provide a ____ of recent writing so that your English level can be assessed.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The committee will ____ the process by which the decision was made.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doing so will probably provoke a strong negative ____ from the group's normal readership.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An unexpected ____ was that there was also significant improvement in composition as well as in math for these students during the academic year.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our experience is that small businesses (especially those newly formed) ____ to propose unrealistically low indirect costs.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The chairman needs to ____ a better meeting next time. The last one was very disorganized.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the ____ was not deliberate and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In many cases, simply stating to the student that the behavior is unacceptable and must not ____ again is sufficient.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a ____ problem they would like to address and collaborate with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must ____ against the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Politicians realize that they can't know everything, so they surround themselves with people who can ____ them.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new ____ could lead to widespread use of solar power.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Begin your paper with a brief description of the storyline, or a brief ____ from it, that suggests or illustrates your thesis.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most people are shocked by the ____ of life in Iraq since the invasion a few years ago.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We hoped to find relevant data on why ____ people donate time and money and others don't.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Younger students usually have no ____ in what they study.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to ____ the material covered by the homework problems in order to pass the quizzes and final examination.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you get a grade below C-, you will need to ____ the course for it to count at all on your major.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most scientists ____ that the life expectancy of people in developed countries will continue to rise.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Niehuss does much to illuminate the enormous ____ of consumer culture on West German women's lives.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new rules will ____ to anyone who has come to Germany in the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some types of ____ are dirty, dangerous or not well-paid. It is often poor immigrants to a country who take such jobs.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The supply of new doctors is getting low. Some remote parts of the country will be without medical services if this ____ does not change.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "High school students who have completed this difficult ____ deserve a reward.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You can buy each ____ on the school supplies list from the bookstore.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The volume of business between Europe and Asia has ____ increased in recent years.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Dr. Glick is an expert in ____ and public health nursing programs and issues.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some students find it difficult to ____ to a new school in a new country.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to ____ a variety of materials to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to intervene in the ____ over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On your first day in a new school it is difficult to ____ all the information that you are given.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Lord Wavell had to ____ as he could not bring about a settlement and he was succeeded by Lord Mountbatten.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The two parties paid for these mistakes through extremely poor ____ in the final national elections.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government minister expressed ____ at her thoughtless comment about 'lazy incompetent teachers'.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Digital Libraries constitute a relatively young scientific field, whose life spans ____ the last fifteen years.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of the new hotel has been well-chosen: halfway between the airport and the beach.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This could substantially change the nature of the Internet we have come to know, to the ____ of both the consumers and the providers of information.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would ____ an automatic decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We have had no chance to ____ changes of this sort systematically, but simply offer them as examples of processes that we expect to be completed.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In this article I will discuss the possible use of ____ speech recognition (ASR) for training students to improve their accents in a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Research into heart disease has revealed a clear pattern: those who smoke too much, drink too much and do not exercise enough are the most likely to ____ from it.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Good teachers must ____ their students as they find them, as they present themselves, walking in the door.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is unclear whether this facility will be able to ____ complete missiles or only some major component.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ is not rare: 99 percent of patients experience a phantom pain after an amputation.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government decided to ____ its economic policy after three years of very slow growth.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It will help to ____ the nuclear powers from developing more advanced and more dangerous weapons.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "One of the most common laments we hear from instructor is that they can't get their students to ____ substantial revisions.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I need to ____ again that you may not use your calculator in the examination.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge ____ regarding the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She finally was able to ____ her true ability with an excellent score in the end of year test.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The past 20 years have seen a ____ increase in our understanding of the biology of cancer.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Be sure to ask if this is a good time to ____ the professor for your specific need.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "People are more ____ to migrate in times of war or economic poverty.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her parents failed to ____ the bad influence of her new friends until it was too late.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Aside from the significant ____ impact of the bill, it carries little weight and makes little difference.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government official wrote to ____ that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He alleged that the state had adopted the policy of attacking the entire independent media ____ than targeting individual journalists as in the past.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, exceed ten per trimester is liable to ____ the course.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Seed cleaning is not an operation that requires a large ____ of labor.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The proposal is unlikely to ____ the tension between them.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The most basic technique to ____ is observational drawing skills.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Politics is still a ____ male profession.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your group will need to investigate the ____ characteristics of your city (such as mountains and lakes).", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The numbers of overweight and obese children worldwide are expected to climb ____ by 2010.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This project involves students in the process of learning in an attempt to ____ their skills and their successes across all areas of the course.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He naturally failed to ____ the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy ____ to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In the 20th century, if you wanted to kill lots of people, you needed a government ____ to do it.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Employees interested in participating in a ____ tax sheltered annuity program should contact their personnel officer.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There are ____ 350 students in high school. I'm not sure of the exact number.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some doctors have suggested that their training should be less theoretical and of more ____ use.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For the last 30 years scientists have been searching for a good ____ to gasoline (petrol) as a fuel to run cars.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to impose an ____ crisis upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The time has come, however, to quit spending time and money supporting ____ technologies and to concentrate on delivering better service.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To set up a practice test, I'd ____ a zero point test with questions from the year before in random order with random answers.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government official wrote to ____ that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His research helped establish that identical DNA sequences may ____ differently depending on context and condition.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Every ____ effort will be made to accommodate properly documented special needs.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ optional parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to enlarge the amount of land ____ for pasture.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Everyone should ____ together to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are approximately 350 students in high school. I'm not sure of the ____ number.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The supervisor perceived Pullard as an incompetent employee, but did not ____ that he might be a security problem.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a contemporary problem they would like to address and ____ with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If he is correct this would certainly be an ____ solution to an ancient problem.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Administrators and supervisors are expected to see that those who report to them are informed about, understand and ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A small ____ of the government were against the Prime Minister's plan, but they were outvoted.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new government proposals also ____ that all unemployed young people attend a three-week training course once a year.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to protest about the government's decision to ____ the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Please ____ the Timetable for class times and locations.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It took the Brazilian football player a little while to adjust to the ____ and hardness of the English football league.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "How can educators ____ instruction to maximize the learning of all students?", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The income of a soccer player in one week is many times higher than what most people ____ in a whole year.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many people think that the government's proposals to reduce teenage crime are ____ and will not work.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Buying a lunch ticket in advance will ____ you to a free drink.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "During ____ stages of a planning process, review and crosscheck the goals and objectives in the plan elements so that they do not contradict one another.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ phase of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school is will continue to ____ problems in its attempt to attract new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This article will only ____ the issues rather than present a detailed analysis with proofs.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Performance in the money markets has been consistent in recent months, but prices are expected to ____ in the near future.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If your ____ is not relevant at all to the subject line, start a new thread with a fresh subject line.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most older cultures seem to accept volcanoes as a natural part of life and ____ their habits accordingly.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people believe that harsh prison penalties for young criminals ____ natural justice.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to ____ the scope of the problem.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When morality comes up against profit, it is ____ profit that loses.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's potential and her ____ place in life.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great distance from her primary focus as an ____ for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is a very clear ____ in the school for expelling students who do not follow the rules.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "At lunchtime students ____ to all parts of the school building and play areas.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We cannot allow a few disaffected children to continually ____ the education of the majority of the class.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The xenon atoms need to ____ to a speed of 30 km/s.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a very ____ example for demonstration purposes. However, the effect is similar for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Any student who continues to do poor work or show a bad attitude is put on a ____. If the ____ is broken, then the student is asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government's election ____ is a classic case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not the government's ____ to supervise what people are doing when they are online.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students worked in groups to prove (or disprove) a ____ of mathematical statements.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is a ____ that Japanese girls are quiet. You should hear them on the bus on a school trip!", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "sometimes", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This validation will identify him/her as a \"special student\" and will ____ him/her to the use of additional university facilities, such as the union building and the gym, and to free admissions for selected lectures.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government survey produced a wide ____ of responses.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Fish farming is an ____ that should go some way to compensating for the reduction of fish in the oceans.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These two-word verbs ____ one other problem, besides not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Be sure to ask if this is a good time to ____ the professor for your specific need.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They knew the ____ was inappropriate, but they were not sure how to react.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A company's success or continuation should not ____ on the service of outside in____ent contractors.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not ____ from the essential requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "How do we approach the essential and ____ problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Ambition was not an ____ of the female characters in his earlier films.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its ____ Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum standard for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There are many attempts to ____ more women and minorities to the field, but people's perceptions must be altered before changes can happen.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The best ____ in learning a new language is to find a girlfriend or boyfriend who speaks it!", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "From my ____ as a teacher and parent, I would say that her difficulties in school are due to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not our ____ to send guests away without offering them something to eat.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The final ____ of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But the mice did not ____ thorough cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We will not ____ unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to engage in public service.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government did not proceed with the recommendations ____ the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ was too much for some, and owners were forced to sell their homes at a reduced price.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to ____ its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Howard has many chances to ____ into a better father and husband, but he fails to do so.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You need to include more detail. Your report has lots of general statements but very few ____ facts.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to dedicate herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to ____ serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "control"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The documentation must ____ of a comprehensive, typed report that states a specific, current diagnosis.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the ____ did not emerge until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The fact that she doesn't speak English did much to ____ the situation.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our experience is that small businesses (especially those newly formed) ____ to propose unrealistically low indirect costs.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a cause of a conflict from a ____ of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was ____ a huge amount for a programme that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Food irradiation can be an important tool in the war ____ illness and death from foodborne diseases.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will facilitate ____ and development in our district communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many talented local young people have had to ____ graduate or professional education because of lack of access to such programs.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Poverty has been a ____ problem in the United States for many years.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to condemn but often hard to define. This is partly because the ____ rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The students ____ that I promised to show a DVD on in class today, but I cannot remember doing so.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The older population of the U.S. and the world is growing rapidly, and these large numbers will represent a major ____ for society in general.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Since it was founded in 1999, the partnership program has been a ____ element in the dramatic increase in applications to the College.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is a particular ____ to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your ____ is to learn the English words that will help you be successful in your school subjects.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We should never praise or blame any person on ____ of outward actions that are common to all; but only on ____ of their principles.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is a highly ____ view of the symbolic nature of physical reality.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This opinion is subject to ____ revision before publication in the university journal.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The shareholders were not pleased with the company's ____ in the last quarter of the year.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Check the ____ below for specific dates and starting times.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There are ____ of things that the new government needs to change when it comes into power.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to ____ about the government's decision to raise the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He rightly concludes that the end of the Cold War failed to ____ significant changes in the Horn of Africa or to improve the mutual security of states.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Sometimes it becomes more important to ____ tried-and-tested methods and habits rather than allocate more resources.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the funding is from personal or family funds, you will need to obtain a current bank statement showing that you have enough funds to ____ expenses.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Car companies spend a considerable ____ of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your answers ____ a lack of care and effort.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A rich parent has made a large ____ so that the school can buy new computers.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "All this progress was a ____ of the advance of technology and also of advances in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "ratio", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This document explains why it is important to conduct a ____ assessment during a sustainability project.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to observe how icebergs in a ____ corner of Antarctica can disrupt an entire marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The price of stamps will increase only if the total volume of mail does not ____ and the postal service does not become more efficient.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the classroom doors to make them less easy to break down.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When reporting scores, both the student's ____ and the number of students in the class must be stated.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The cost of transporting diesel fuel to operate machines in the arctic ____ is very high, typically 2-4 times world market prices.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An international school is a place that cannot ____ if there is prejudice that certain groups of students are better than others.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "From then on, the government tried to ____ the communists of being enemies of the fatherland.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning technique to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We need to ____ a test to measure the improvement in ESL students' English from one year to the next.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was a very ____ test. Everyone got 100%.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The report shows how the mass media ____ affect adolescent smoking rates.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "sometimes", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "One enjoyable way to improve in English is to do ____ of reading.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A very effective way to check how the use of an English word is to look in Google for pages that ____ it.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of the school behind the car park is for seniors only.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also ____ to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "One study found that anemia was a strong predictor of other ____ problems that were not present at the time anemia was first detected.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our teacher showed us an ____ of The Simpsons in ESL class yesterday.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Reducing taxation is the second ____ of the government's 5-year financial plan.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Game reasoning is ____ moral reasoning that occurs in the context of competitive sports, and perhaps elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "They were unable to ____ the distribution of food supplies because of the deteriorating security situation.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first and only reliable line of defense ____ the acquisition or use of \"suitcase nuclear weapons\" by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The pictures presented aspects of the objects they could not ____ from the equations alone.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "However, because The Dream intends to interest both lay and professional readers, it is unfortunate that she failed to ____ a glossary of significant terms.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "How people ____ to music is subjective. What sounds good to one person may sound terrible to another.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's no use trying to ____ me that your father speaks 10 languages. I just don't believe you.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a strong ____ between what the government promised to do and what it has actually achieved.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She didn't study for the vocabulary test, so ____ she got a low score.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It has no alternative but to ____ to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to support Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is English expression which claims: All roads lead to Rome. This means that there is more than one ____ to fame and success in life.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To remain eligible for financial aid, recipients are required to show satisfactory ____ toward a degree according to the guidelines listed below.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The book focuses on the ____ role the family plays as teenagers navigate the difficult transition from childhood to adulthood.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was a time when priests were experiencing financial crisis and the Church was unable to ____ many of their expenses.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What do I need to ____ in deciding if this course is right for me?", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We spent the ____ lesson talking about the past continuous tense. It was so boring.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Melting glaciers will ____ Alpine ski resorts within 45 years, says report.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government faces a ____ decision: Does it anger the USA or does it anger its European allies?", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This page contains a ____ outline to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He did not ____ to one set of religious beliefs and pioneered a new artistic style known today as symbolism.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The outcome of our ____ is that most students are against school uniform.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ was too much for some, and owners were forced to sell their homes at a reduced price.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is easy to ____ the government for its failures, but no-one has come up with any better ideas.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Though all of them are presented in English, there is a significant ____ in clarity between the various reports.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many tourists to foreign countries buy a ____ book to help them speak a few words of the language.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The researchers did not ____ people with known chronic disease from their study.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Among other duties, Wren and his team of designers and builders were responsible for the upkeep or alteration of all ____ buildings.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school has installed emergency buttons in each classroom as a ____ against intruders.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is especially true from an investing ____ when repeating the same strategy could be a road to utter disaster.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people say that the ____ of banning smoking in public places will be that more people will smoke at home. This will be worse for the children.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to help each other, but is spite also part of the human condition?", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teacher trainees will need to master problem-solving strategies that offer clear ____ solutions to issues that affect those in poverty.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Until recently there have been few sources of information about the morphological and syntactic ____ of the Kam language.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The significant differences between the traditional and non-traditional student has prompted the question whether institutions need to ____ their teaching methods to fit the needs of the non-traditional student.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a ____ for selection.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Copying from the internet has grown on a large ____ in recent years.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is known that organizations do not ____ readily or easily; many organizations that change do so in ways that are neither successful nor effective.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unfortunately, heroines of this sort are not numerous in oral tales, and do not ____ at all in any of the Grimm tales.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The decision to make cannabis legal in small amounts is a significant ____ in the government's policy.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Unfortunately, many drug users ____ from prison only to find themselves back there a few months later. This is because they cannot find or keep a job, and need to steal to finance their drug-taking habits.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to ____ about the government's decision to raise the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "People have been trying for decades or maybe even centuries in an attempt to bring this ____ problem to an end.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to know a little more about the ____ before you criticize the government's decision.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Journalists were able to ____ the government's secret plan to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ a new campaign to reduce teenage drinking.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My family can't ____ a new house. They're so expensive in Germany.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a ____ of its books to display to teachers.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teachers ____ that the school administration is secretly planning to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He came to the conclusion that Mexico's constitutions did not last because they simply did not ____ to Mexico's customs and traditions.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These ____ and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable expense to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "delay", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "lateness", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Asian companies are good at building small cars but will never ____ the mainstream US car market.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please do not ____ me. I know what I said is correct.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government survey produced a wide ____ of responses.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In this assignment, you will need to ____ an array of numbers, so that your computer code executes correctly.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you ____ the stairs by the nurse's office, you will see the cafeteria in front of you.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This unnecessary war will ____ the government plans to reduce tax.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most ____ decision of his career in order to assure his political survival.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "No matter how good the lawyer's intuition and ability to ____ himself or herself, the lawyer will not succeed unless he or she can analyze logically.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "So maybe people who see media studies as too general, too loose, too intellectually ____ have a point.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Teaching is the ____ of the people who work at FIS.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His father is going to ____ him at the office during the vacation so that he can make a bit of money.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Follow these recommended times for storage in the freezer to enjoy the best quality in flavor and texture and to ____ good nutritive value.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is planning to make a ____ tomorrow morning on its discussions the doctors' union.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I find it very difficult to ____ his bad manners.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Arming the Bosnian Serbs was regarded as a political ____ than a military issue.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Learners' perception of complexity had a negative ____ on successful problem solving performance.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This page unites the texts on various aspects of the history of law in the ____ world.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government must be prepared for an attack from people who ____ its decision.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When he left home he planned to ____ from Christianity to Buddhism, but then he decided he didn't believe in any god.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many of the faculty and students we talked with wanted to ____ anonymous and asked that they not be listed by name in our report.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the ____ use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What motives have thus incited him to ____ all the hardships and temptations he encountered on his way from a miserable life to an honorable one.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When all the edits are done, click the button to ____ the changes to the database.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "commit", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I ____ his strange behaviour recently is the result of his parents' divorce.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This ____ is subject to formal revision before publication in the university journal.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many students look for ____ work between leaving school and starting university.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so ____ to allowing ordinary parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to ____ the political support needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The tale ends with Gilgamesh, at the end of his ____ standing before the gates of Uruk.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Could you use informal writing tasks to ____ thinking and learning?", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "One of the major goals of Women's Studies over the past 25 years has been to ____ the work of women writers from past times.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a strong ____ between what the government promised to do and what it has actually achieved.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, ____ is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government is going to ____ a law that will prohibit smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As the number of old people increases, so has the ____ that there is not enough money in the health system to take proper care of them.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If submitted in other languages, an English ____ must accompany the submission.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first exhaust all possibilities for Federal and state financial aid programs before seeking ____ loans.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is an excellent piece of work. You ____ your ideas very clearly.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has some ____ plans to reduce income tax in the next 5 years.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Upon completion of your program requirements, you will need to ____ for a license to teach in the state of Ohio.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As the advisor, you often have other responsibilities that do not always ____ giving undivided attention to the organization.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She finally was able to ____ her true ability with an excellent score in the end of year test.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A common science experiment for young people is to investigate the ____ of plants under different soil, light and water conditions.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In my ____ the government's argument for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People with eye problems often cannot ____ the colors red and green.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was the result of his ____ that Brazil could afford scientific institutions.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The doctor began to realize that her patient was not telling the whole ____ about what was wrong.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to ____ information about patterns of ties among social actors.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to ____ higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This paper documents preliminary findings from a nationwide ____ that investigates substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Such activity cannot be considered an adequate ____ for excellence in teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company's ____ in the second half of the year is to increase its export business.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We should not ____ the costs, minimize the benefits of what we have already achieved, or downplay the risk of failure to persevere.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Infinite power is so ____ and incomprehensible an idea that the mind of man must necessarily be bewildered in the contemplation of it.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some information is collected on our ____ by outside agencies in order to provide services to our visitors.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The greatest ____ that we face is to reduce global warming.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As yet there has been no ____ example of the sighting of a spacecraft from another world.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "credible", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "believable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of ____ like a camera, it helps to have a diagram to look at.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This brochure was created to help home owners and land managers ____ hazardous defects in trees and to suggest possible corrective actions.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government is thinking about introducing courses to ____ young people how to be good parents.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How many planet/planet collisions do you presume will come from the M31 ____ - or do you think we will be smoothly assimilated?", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is important to ____ that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all necessary signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Once you've chosen the course or courses you wish to take, you should contact COM so that we can ____ a place for you.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an optional tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the ____ of restoration.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The writer was not careful when taking notes because he does not understand what plagiarism is, or because he is not ____ of what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ that led to the train crash are being investigated by the police.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a lively debate in the country at the moment on whether cannabis should be made ____ or not.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Significant progress has been toward reaching this ____ through the broad workforce planning effort as well as specific unit managerial decisions.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many people have complained about the ____ security procedures that have been introduced to UK airports.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They were unable to ____ the distribution of food supplies because of the deteriorating security situation.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is confident that the summer ____ cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you want to ____ the chess club, please sign your name on the list below.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the ____ reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It circles the theater so that you can ____ projectors at any spot on the dome, whereas before we were limited to placing them toward the back of the room.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school does a lot to ____ new families, with information meetings, translation services, etc.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ a lot of money in a new arts and technology block.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The first ____ to produce a revised policy started during the mid-1980s and failed to culminate in a new agreement.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, ____ a huge debt to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A supervisor must not ignore, delay, or inappropriately ____ an student's request for assistance.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot ____ it.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Before doing a longer piece of writing it is usually a good idea to make an ____ to organize your main ideas.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "That's the third time she's been late in the last week. I think I need to ____ the matter with her parents.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our experience is that small businesses (especially those newly formed) ____ to propose unrealistically low indirect costs.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to ____ the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The book is at its best when it delves energetically into some particular event, and draws out its ____ meaning with reference to the grand themes.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you can't do your homework, you should ask your parents to ____ you.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The need for an alternative ____ to teacher certification has become evident.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ heavier punishment for dropping litter in the streets.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ you to prepare more carefully for tests.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We are going to ____ this photograph to poster size and put it on the classroom wall.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The latest trend ____ the girls in the school is to wear different colour socks.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse global society will ____ as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ between Russia's dominant military power and our own inferior power could not be bridged overnight.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Bernstein thinks the survey is very important to students and that schools should not ____ it.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "My ____ tells me that there is more to her learning problems than the parents are willing to say.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the ____ of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to ____ its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the 20th century, if you wanted to kill lots of people, you needed a government ____ to do it.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "However, because The Dream intends to interest both lay and professional readers, it is unfortunate that she failed to ____ a glossary of significant terms.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students will learn to ____ what epidemiologists mean when they say that an exposure and an outcome are associated.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Roman Catholic Church along with the main Protestant denominations in Europe did not ____ the slave trade.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first and only reliable line of defense ____ the acquisition or use of \"suitcase nuclear weapons\" by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting threaten to raise water levels and ____ flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I assume his strange behaviour ____ is the result of his parents' divorce.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is my ____ intention to remain with my department for at least two years.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students engaging in scheduled curricular work have ____ over other students.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In many cases, simply stating to the student that the behavior is unacceptable and must not ____ again is sufficient.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company was unable to ____ its recent good trade figures.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The comprehensive and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round ____ of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Access to the data network is both an essential tool for university life and work, and a ____ privilege.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "valuable", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Do not ____ the serious error of believing you can pass the course without doing the coursework.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "commit", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to make inferences and hold causal beliefs, even though it is not rational.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a ____ consequence of having free will.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A frequent ____ in editing is to fix a word or phrase at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His written work is actually very good, but he has ____ problems with the difficult English spelling system.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "While I am not in favor of teaching creationism in ____ schools, I am also not averse to having it presented and examined.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Smoking will probably ____ in popularity in most western countries now that smoking bans are in force.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was a loud argument in the cafeteria today. I had to ____ before it turned into a fight.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly ____ if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an extremely minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's a total ____ that young girls are being pressured into near-starving themselves into being too thin.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Having access to the laptop does seem to have substantially increased the overall feeling of having ____ resources to do the job.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "On hearing of the terrorist attack the president called an ____ meeting of his top advisers.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The airport police always ____ the need for everyone to be vigilant with their suitcases and other bags.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are ____ 350 students in high school. I'm not sure of the exact number.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Bassett did not ____ to take on responsibilities outside the classroom.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some politicians ____ that too much immigration will result in fewer jobs for the people born in the country.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The scientists advising EPA said they believe there is a ____ chance that the corn is an allergen.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was not the ____ noise of the battle-front that night; every soldier knew that a something different was going to happen.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These instruction and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are ____ (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is a particular privilege to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who ____ all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "consume", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to use, or use up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The university should not ____ students who take an extra year to complete their studies as lazy.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her parents failed to ____ the bad influence of her new friends until it was too late.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to ____ the cost of complying with new requirements regarding data recording.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When societies ____ into violence the result is all too familiar: the destruction of life and infrastructure, gross abuses of human rights.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The two departments have failed to ____ and coordinate their efforts in implementing the laws and regulations on the use of wetland areas.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The unemployment figures ____ that the recent changes in tax have been successful.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He has lost the desire to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, ____ devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not perceive it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to ____ a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company has the liberty to ____ employees without giving a reason during the first 6 months of their employment.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "With her departure we have decided to ____ teaching Spanish this fall as we await the committee report.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Germany is no longer a ____ society. Between 15 - 20% of its population is non-German.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Now ____ that a box contains one fair coin and one coin with a head on each side.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best footballers can ____ many thousands of pounds every day.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If the human body is weak or cold, it is less able to ____ infection.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Describe the study in ____ sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is worth investigation.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This ____ provides an overview of several aspects of Egyptian culture.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If he is correct this would certainly be an ____ solution to an ancient problem.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The internet is a vast ____ for today's students.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most people have a vague ____ of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most governments refuse to ____ with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Being forced to speak before they are ready can ____ some adults' enjoyment and success in learning a language.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "People who move from the countryside to a large city often take time to adjust to ____ living.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase ____ tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The report shows how the mass media ____ affect adolescent smoking rates.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable statistic and you should simply ____ it.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "At a certain point in your journey, you might discover that the ____ you chose is just too vast.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The USA is designing a spaceship that will land on Mars and ____ its polar regions.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The women did not ____ emotionally to the comedy, but the men did, Filipowicz concludes.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The best survival ____ for one part of the organization is usually not the best ____ for another.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teacher left an ____ that no homework was to be set in her absence.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The primary ____ of the Management Information Systems Department is to prepare students for exciting and challenging careers in the information technology.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police are trying to ____ the men seen on camera breaking the bus shelter.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "APA offers specific recommendations for eliminating ____ in language concerning race, disability, and sexuality.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The book focuses on the key role the family plays as teenagers navigate the difficult ____ from childhood to adulthood.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of formal grammar rules does always not ____ with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the classroom doors to make them less easy to break down.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate poor work that is ____ to laziness and poor work that is ____ to inability.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase level of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to ____ its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you offend ____ the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very technical email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe ____ did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "China is able to ____ goods cheaply because labour costs are low.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The expulsion of a student for smoking in the toilets caused a big ____ in the school.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Those who could not transform, chose not to, or who were considered a threat to the ____ were imprisoned and eliminated.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Its plot centers on how the ____ between two female \"mates\" is almost broken because both love the same man.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is during adolescence that clear gender differences ____ which might contribute to the varying rates of depression.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government is having difficulty trying to ____ the reasons for its change of policy.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of ____ guidance, but instead thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will descend by the ____ of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Important politicians are usually surrounded by bodyguards whose job is to ____ them.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The bulk of the ____ money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to ____ greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In an era of privatisation and market rule we are facing the fact that ____ments will have to ____ a bit more.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Web sites such as Wikipedia certainly ____ the finding of information, although not all of it is reliable.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and harsh treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of ____ White jurors.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "sometimes", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ASVAB is a mental ability test given to all ____ entrants to the Armed Services.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Their acquaintance, therefore, it may be presumed, did not ____ till towards the end of this year 1754.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}]]